{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946778933495","data":{"timestamp":" 946778933495"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f740db00-34af-446c-883a-c7ada2fda8e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946778937818","data":{"timestamp":" 946778937818"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f740db00-34af-446c-883a-c7ada2fda8e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946778942238","data":{"timestamp":" 946778942238"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f740db00-34af-446c-883a-c7ada2fda8e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946778946588","data":{"timestamp":" 946778946588"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f740db00-34af-446c-883a-c7ada2fda8e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946778950548","data":{"timestamp":" 946778950548"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f740db00-34af-446c-883a-c7ada2fda8e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946778956049","data":{"timestamp":" 946778956049"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f740db00-34af-446c-883a-c7ada2fda8e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946778960912","data":{"timestamp":" 946778960912"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f740db00-34af-446c-883a-c7ada2fda8e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946778965657","data":{"timestamp":" 946778965657"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f740db00-34af-446c-883a-c7ada2fda8e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946778970581","data":{"timestamp":" 946778970580"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f740db00-34af-446c-883a-c7ada2fda8e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946778974575","data":{"timestamp":" 946778974575"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f740db00-34af-446c-883a-c7ada2fda8e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946778978535","data":{"timestamp":" 946778978535"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f740db00-34af-446c-883a-c7ada2fda8e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946778982531","data":{"timestamp":" 946778982531"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f740db00-34af-446c-883a-c7ada2fda8e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946778990437","data":{"timestamp":" 946778990437"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f740db00-34af-446c-883a-c7ada2fda8e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946778994670","data":{"timestamp":" 946778994670"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f740db00-34af-446c-883a-c7ada2fda8e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946778998248","data":{"timestamp":" 946778998248"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f740db00-34af-446c-883a-c7ada2fda8e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779002329","data":{"timestamp":" 946779002329"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f740db00-34af-446c-883a-c7ada2fda8e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-W"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779006880","data":{"timestamp":" 946779006880"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f740db00-34af-446c-883a-c7ada2fda8e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-E-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779010696","data":{"timestamp":" 946779010696"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f740db00-34af-446c-883a-c7ada2fda8e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779015356","data":{"timestamp":" 946779015356"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f740db00-34af-446c-883a-c7ada2fda8e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-Z-T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779021167","data":{"timestamp":" 946779021167"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f740db00-34af-446c-883a-c7ada2fda8e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779025736","data":{"timestamp":" 946779025735"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f740db00-34af-446c-883a-c7ada2fda8e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779031895","data":{"timestamp":" 946779031895"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f740db00-34af-446c-883a-c7ada2fda8e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779035730","data":{"timestamp":" 946779035730"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f740db00-34af-446c-883a-c7ada2fda8e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779039760","data":{"timestamp":" 946779039760"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f740db00-34af-446c-883a-c7ada2fda8e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779045549","data":{"timestamp":" 946779045548"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f740db00-34af-446c-883a-c7ada2fda8e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779089656","data":{"timestamp":" 946779089656"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" ae601f77-5017-49e9-bdb5-64fa9f5f527b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chekechea_chekechea-huruma-mafuta-refu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chekechea"," userResponse":" chekechea"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779131266","data":{"timestamp":" 946779131266"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" ae601f77-5017-49e9-bdb5-64fa9f5f527b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" huzuni_huzuni-tai-wazi-sura"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" huzuni"," userResponse":" huzuni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779158654","data":{"timestamp":" 946779158654"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" ae601f77-5017-49e9-bdb5-64fa9f5f527b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chekechea_nne-chekechea-mpenzi-neno"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chekechea"," userResponse":" nne"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779161337","data":{"timestamp":" 946779161337"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" ae601f77-5017-49e9-bdb5-64fa9f5f527b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chekechea_nne-chekechea-mpenzi-neno"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chekechea"," userResponse":" chekechea"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779183430","data":{"timestamp":" 946779183430"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" ae601f77-5017-49e9-bdb5-64fa9f5f527b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chekechea_mifugo-samahani-neno-chekechea"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chekechea"," userResponse":" mifugo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779186433","data":{"timestamp":" 946779186432"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" ae601f77-5017-49e9-bdb5-64fa9f5f527b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chekechea_mifugo-samahani-neno-chekechea"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chekechea"," userResponse":" samahani"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779189248","data":{"timestamp":" 946779189248"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" ae601f77-5017-49e9-bdb5-64fa9f5f527b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chekechea_mifugo-samahani-neno-chekechea"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chekechea"," userResponse":" neno"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779192165","data":{"timestamp":" 946779192165"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" ae601f77-5017-49e9-bdb5-64fa9f5f527b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chekechea_mifugo-samahani-neno-chekechea"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chekechea"," userResponse":" chekechea"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779220883","data":{"timestamp":" 946779220883"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" ae601f77-5017-49e9-bdb5-64fa9f5f527b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kubwa_kubwa-yule-tafadhali-hadi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kubwa"," userResponse":" kubwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779248847","data":{"timestamp":" 946779248847"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" ae601f77-5017-49e9-bdb5-64fa9f5f527b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chupa_mashamba-chupa-barua-chai"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chupa"," userResponse":" mashamba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779251525","data":{"timestamp":" 946779251525"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" ae601f77-5017-49e9-bdb5-64fa9f5f527b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chupa_mashamba-chupa-barua-chai"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chupa"," userResponse":" chupa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779303855","data":{"timestamp":" 946779303855"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" ae601f77-5017-49e9-bdb5-64fa9f5f527b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mahali_mbali-nyumba-mahali-maisha"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mahali"," userResponse":" nyumba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779307121","data":{"timestamp":" 946779307121"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" ae601f77-5017-49e9-bdb5-64fa9f5f527b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mahali_mbali-nyumba-mahali-maisha"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mahali"," userResponse":" mahali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779329068","data":{"timestamp":" 946779329068"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" ae601f77-5017-49e9-bdb5-64fa9f5f527b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia_harakisha-makofi-kaka-Ambia"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Ambia"," userResponse":" harakisha"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779331743","data":{"timestamp":" 946779331743"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" ae601f77-5017-49e9-bdb5-64fa9f5f527b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia_harakisha-makofi-kaka-Ambia"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Ambia"," userResponse":" makofi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779334414","data":{"timestamp":" 946779334414"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" ae601f77-5017-49e9-bdb5-64fa9f5f527b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia_harakisha-makofi-kaka-Ambia"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Ambia"," userResponse":" kaka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779337096","data":{"timestamp":" 946779337096"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" ae601f77-5017-49e9-bdb5-64fa9f5f527b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia_harakisha-makofi-kaka-Ambia"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Ambia"," userResponse":" Ambia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779390315","data":{"timestamp":" 946779390315"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" ae601f77-5017-49e9-bdb5-64fa9f5f527b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sana_kwenda-sana-wakati-za"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" sana"," userResponse":" kwenda"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779393275","data":{"timestamp":" 946779393275"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" ae601f77-5017-49e9-bdb5-64fa9f5f527b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sana_kwenda-sana-wakati-za"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" sana"," userResponse":" sana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779507806","data":{"timestamp":" 946779507805"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" ae601f77-5017-49e9-bdb5-64fa9f5f527b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" sana_kwenda-sana-wakati-za"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779507916","data":{"timestamp":" 946779507915"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" ae601f77-5017-49e9-bdb5-64fa9f5f527b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779518640","data":{"timestamp":" 946779518639"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779519695","data":{"timestamp":" 946779519695"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779522832","data":{"timestamp":" 946779522832"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779523875","data":{"timestamp":" 946779523875"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779526434","data":{"timestamp":" 946779526434"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779526757","data":{"timestamp":" 946779526757"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779527547","data":{"timestamp":" 946779527547"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779529986","data":{"timestamp":" 946779529986"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779532198","data":{"timestamp":" 946779532198"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779533232","data":{"timestamp":" 946779533232"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779535820","data":{"timestamp":" 946779535820"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779536123","data":{"timestamp":" 946779536123"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779536957","data":{"timestamp":" 946779536957"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779539718","data":{"timestamp":" 946779539718"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779542913","data":{"timestamp":" 946779542913"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779543951","data":{"timestamp":" 946779543951"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779546663","data":{"timestamp":" 946779546663"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779547695","data":{"timestamp":" 946779547695"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779551178","data":{"timestamp":" 946779551178"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779552220","data":{"timestamp":" 946779552219"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779556013","data":{"timestamp":" 946779556013"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779557055","data":{"timestamp":" 946779557055"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779562655","data":{"timestamp":" 946779562655"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779563696","data":{"timestamp":" 946779563696"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779566775","data":{"timestamp":" 946779566774"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779567840","data":{"timestamp":" 946779567840"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779570993","data":{"timestamp":" 946779570992"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779572045","data":{"timestamp":" 946779572045"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779575774","data":{"timestamp":" 946779575774"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779576805","data":{"timestamp":" 946779576805"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779579423","data":{"timestamp":" 946779579423"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779579721","data":{"timestamp":" 946779579721"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779580553","data":{"timestamp":" 946779580553"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779582031","data":{"timestamp":" 946779582031"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779582903","data":{"timestamp":" 946779582903"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779585402","data":{"timestamp":" 946779585402"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779588134","data":{"timestamp":" 946779588134"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779588221","data":{"timestamp":" 946779588221"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779589262","data":{"timestamp":" 946779589262"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779591609","data":{"timestamp":" 946779591609"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779594104","data":{"timestamp":" 946779594104"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779595130","data":{"timestamp":" 946779595130"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779598608","data":{"timestamp":" 946779598608"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779599641","data":{"timestamp":" 946779599640"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779602423","data":{"timestamp":" 946779602423"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779602620","data":{"timestamp":" 946779602620"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779603554","data":{"timestamp":" 946779603554"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779606074","data":{"timestamp":" 946779606074"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779609402","data":{"timestamp":" 946779609402"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779609470","data":{"timestamp":" 946779609470"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 8027efc1-5c08-4521-aee4-08124f753d97"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779629625","data":{"timestamp":" 946779629625"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" df0f3172-073e-4433-bff6-0bc4c838f2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_9_7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779637117","data":{"timestamp":" 946779637117"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" df0f3172-073e-4433-bff6-0bc4c838f2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_9_7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779643756","data":{"timestamp":" 946779643756"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" df0f3172-073e-4433-bff6-0bc4c838f2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_4_8_5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779651335","data":{"timestamp":" 946779651335"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" df0f3172-073e-4433-bff6-0bc4c838f2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_4_8_5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779657944","data":{"timestamp":" 946779657944"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" df0f3172-073e-4433-bff6-0bc4c838f2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_7_4_8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779664555","data":{"timestamp":" 946779664555"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" df0f3172-073e-4433-bff6-0bc4c838f2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_4_2_6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779672031","data":{"timestamp":" 946779672031"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" df0f3172-073e-4433-bff6-0bc4c838f2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_4_2_6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779678647","data":{"timestamp":" 946779678647"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" df0f3172-073e-4433-bff6-0bc4c838f2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_8_6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779686117","data":{"timestamp":" 946779686117"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" df0f3172-073e-4433-bff6-0bc4c838f2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_8_6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779692727","data":{"timestamp":" 946779692727"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" df0f3172-073e-4433-bff6-0bc4c838f2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_4_7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779699323","data":{"timestamp":" 946779699323"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" df0f3172-073e-4433-bff6-0bc4c838f2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_3_9_2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779705955","data":{"timestamp":" 946779705954"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" df0f3172-073e-4433-bff6-0bc4c838f2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_2_8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779712592","data":{"timestamp":" 946779712592"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" df0f3172-073e-4433-bff6-0bc4c838f2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_8_1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779720085","data":{"timestamp":" 946779720085"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" df0f3172-073e-4433-bff6-0bc4c838f2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_8_1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779729078","data":{"timestamp":" 946779729078"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" df0f3172-073e-4433-bff6-0bc4c838f2ff"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_5_8_1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779739166","data":{"timestamp":" 946779739166"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779741346","data":{"timestamp":" 946779741345"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779743526","data":{"timestamp":" 946779743525"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779746763","data":{"timestamp":" 946779746763"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779749046","data":{"timestamp":" 946779749046"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779751336","data":{"timestamp":" 946779751336"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779754252","data":{"timestamp":" 946779754252"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779756428","data":{"timestamp":" 946779756428"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779758646","data":{"timestamp":" 946779758646"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779761897","data":{"timestamp":" 946779761896"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779763998","data":{"timestamp":" 946779763997"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779766092","data":{"timestamp":" 946779766092"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779769076","data":{"timestamp":" 946779769075"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779771294","data":{"timestamp":" 946779771293"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779773548","data":{"timestamp":" 946779773548"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779776586","data":{"timestamp":" 946779776585"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779778964","data":{"timestamp":" 946779778963"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779781289","data":{"timestamp":" 946779781289"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779784333","data":{"timestamp":" 946779784332"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779786491","data":{"timestamp":" 946779786490"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779788617","data":{"timestamp":" 946779788616"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779791804","data":{"timestamp":" 946779791803"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779794023","data":{"timestamp":" 946779794023"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779796230","data":{"timestamp":" 946779796230"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779799445","data":{"timestamp":" 946779799444"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779801866","data":{"timestamp":" 946779801866"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779804296","data":{"timestamp":" 946779804295"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779807498","data":{"timestamp":" 946779807497"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779809757","data":{"timestamp":" 946779809757"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779812021","data":{"timestamp":" 946779812021"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779815008","data":{"timestamp":" 946779815007"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779817252","data":{"timestamp":" 946779817252"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779819498","data":{"timestamp":" 946779819497"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779822534","data":{"timestamp":" 946779822533"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779824931","data":{"timestamp":" 946779824930"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779827325","data":{"timestamp":" 946779827324"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779830458","data":{"timestamp":" 946779830458"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779832831","data":{"timestamp":" 946779832831"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779835212","data":{"timestamp":" 946779835211"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779838212","data":{"timestamp":" 946779838211"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779840520","data":{"timestamp":" 946779840519"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779842786","data":{"timestamp":" 946779842786"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779846024","data":{"timestamp":" 946779846024"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779848310","data":{"timestamp":" 946779848310"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779850581","data":{"timestamp":" 946779850580"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779853982","data":{"timestamp":" 946779853981"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779856436","data":{"timestamp":" 946779856435"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779858901","data":{"timestamp":" 946779858901"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779861801","data":{"timestamp":" 946779861801"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779864007","data":{"timestamp":" 946779864006"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779866212","data":{"timestamp":" 946779866211"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779869641","data":{"timestamp":" 946779869641"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779871960","data":{"timestamp":" 946779871960"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779874264","data":{"timestamp":" 946779874263"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779877420","data":{"timestamp":" 946779877419"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779879656","data":{"timestamp":" 946779879656"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779881906","data":{"timestamp":" 946779881905"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779884961","data":{"timestamp":" 946779884960"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779887073","data":{"timestamp":" 946779887072"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779889246","data":{"timestamp":" 946779889245"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779892310","data":{"timestamp":" 946779892310"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779894485","data":{"timestamp":" 946779894484"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779896713","data":{"timestamp":" 946779896713"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779899896","data":{"timestamp":" 946779899896"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779902084","data":{"timestamp":" 946779902084"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779904259","data":{"timestamp":" 946779904258"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779907540","data":{"timestamp":" 946779907540"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779909888","data":{"timestamp":" 946779909887"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779912232","data":{"timestamp":" 946779912232"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779915384","data":{"timestamp":" 946779915383"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779917725","data":{"timestamp":" 946779917725"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779920067","data":{"timestamp":" 946779920066"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779923480","data":{"timestamp":" 946779923479"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779923558","data":{"timestamp":" 946779923558"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779939585","data":{"timestamp":" 946779939585"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" c40cce5a-ba0b-4079-ba87-9b2b172d277b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779939632","data":{"timestamp":" 946779939632"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 096a23d1-b39d-4b5c-b874-c3bfc087cc49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDALO"," userResponse":" NDALO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779952937","data":{"timestamp":" 946779952936"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 096a23d1-b39d-4b5c-b874-c3bfc087cc49"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779952989","data":{"timestamp":" 946779952989"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 59bf35b3-3f63-43d6-9f37-5cc0fba70def"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Ndalo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779964719","data":{"timestamp":" 946779964719"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 56ba9746-10a2-4379-8dc7-5a952f96bf4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HELIKOPTA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779970537","data":{"timestamp":" 946779970536"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 56ba9746-10a2-4379-8dc7-5a952f96bf4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HELIKOPTA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779972095","data":{"timestamp":" 946779972095"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 56ba9746-10a2-4379-8dc7-5a952f96bf4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARUFU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779975449","data":{"timestamp":" 946779975449"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 56ba9746-10a2-4379-8dc7-5a952f96bf4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARUFU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779977055","data":{"timestamp":" 946779977055"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 56ba9746-10a2-4379-8dc7-5a952f96bf4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HUJAMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" HUJAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779980917","data":{"timestamp":" 946779980916"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 56ba9746-10a2-4379-8dc7-5a952f96bf4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HUJAMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" START_HUJAMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779981949","data":{"timestamp":" 946779981948"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 56ba9746-10a2-4379-8dc7-5a952f96bf4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HUJAMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" HUJAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779983546","data":{"timestamp":" 946779983545"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 56ba9746-10a2-4379-8dc7-5a952f96bf4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779987060","data":{"timestamp":" 946779987060"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 56ba9746-10a2-4379-8dc7-5a952f96bf4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779988656","data":{"timestamp":" 946779988656"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 56ba9746-10a2-4379-8dc7-5a952f96bf4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARUSI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUSI"," userResponse":" HARUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779993920","data":{"timestamp":" 946779993920"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 56ba9746-10a2-4379-8dc7-5a952f96bf4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARUSI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUSI"," userResponse":" HARUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946779995520","data":{"timestamp":" 946779995520"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 56ba9746-10a2-4379-8dc7-5a952f96bf4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HOSPITALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780004926","data":{"timestamp":" 946780004926"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 56ba9746-10a2-4379-8dc7-5a952f96bf4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HOSPITALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780006480","data":{"timestamp":" 946780006480"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 56ba9746-10a2-4379-8dc7-5a952f96bf4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HUNYWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780010187","data":{"timestamp":" 946780010187"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 56ba9746-10a2-4379-8dc7-5a952f96bf4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HUNYWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780011785","data":{"timestamp":" 946780011784"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 56ba9746-10a2-4379-8dc7-5a952f96bf4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HOHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOHO"," userResponse":" HOHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780016443","data":{"timestamp":" 946780016442"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 56ba9746-10a2-4379-8dc7-5a952f96bf4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HOHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOHO"," userResponse":" HOHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780018053","data":{"timestamp":" 946780018052"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 56ba9746-10a2-4379-8dc7-5a952f96bf4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HEMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEMA"," userResponse":" HEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780020313","data":{"timestamp":" 946780020313"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 56ba9746-10a2-4379-8dc7-5a952f96bf4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HEMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEMA"," userResponse":" HEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780021871","data":{"timestamp":" 946780021871"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 56ba9746-10a2-4379-8dc7-5a952f96bf4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HASIRA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" HASIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780026171","data":{"timestamp":" 946780026171"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 56ba9746-10a2-4379-8dc7-5a952f96bf4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HASIRA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780028181","data":{"timestamp":" 946780028181"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 56ba9746-10a2-4379-8dc7-5a952f96bf4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" HASIRA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780028342","data":{"timestamp":" 946780028342"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 56ba9746-10a2-4379-8dc7-5a952f96bf4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HASIRA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780035425","data":{"timestamp":" 946780035425"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 56ba9746-10a2-4379-8dc7-5a952f96bf4e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" HASIRA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780044598","data":{"timestamp":" 946780044598"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780044972","data":{"timestamp":" 946780044972"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780045454","data":{"timestamp":" 946780045454"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780045808","data":{"timestamp":" 946780045808"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780046223","data":{"timestamp":" 946780046222"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780046714","data":{"timestamp":" 946780046713"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780046950","data":{"timestamp":" 946780046949"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780050077","data":{"timestamp":" 946780050077"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780050111","data":{"timestamp":" 946780050111"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780050824","data":{"timestamp":" 946780050824"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780051226","data":{"timestamp":" 946780051226"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780051530","data":{"timestamp":" 946780051530"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780051740","data":{"timestamp":" 946780051740"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780051938","data":{"timestamp":" 946780051938"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780052260","data":{"timestamp":" 946780052259"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780052497","data":{"timestamp":" 946780052496"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780055595","data":{"timestamp":" 946780055595"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780055997","data":{"timestamp":" 946780055997"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780058523","data":{"timestamp":" 946780058523"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780058735","data":{"timestamp":" 946780058735"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780058948","data":{"timestamp":" 946780058948"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780062510","data":{"timestamp":" 946780062510"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780066307","data":{"timestamp":" 946780066307"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780067343","data":{"timestamp":" 946780067342"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780070129","data":{"timestamp":" 946780070128"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780070512","data":{"timestamp":" 946780070511"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780071002","data":{"timestamp":" 946780071002"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780071356","data":{"timestamp":" 946780071356"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780071770","data":{"timestamp":" 946780071769"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780072254","data":{"timestamp":" 946780072254"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780072487","data":{"timestamp":" 946780072486"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780075661","data":{"timestamp":" 946780075661"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780075698","data":{"timestamp":" 946780075698"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780076421","data":{"timestamp":" 946780076421"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780076827","data":{"timestamp":" 946780076827"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780077136","data":{"timestamp":" 946780077136"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780077345","data":{"timestamp":" 946780077345"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780077548","data":{"timestamp":" 946780077547"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780077872","data":{"timestamp":" 946780077872"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780078106","data":{"timestamp":" 946780078105"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780080768","data":{"timestamp":" 946780080768"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780080824","data":{"timestamp":" 946780080824"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 30db6369-ab9a-4cfb-a133-8a645b3129c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780117634","data":{"timestamp":" 946780117634"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 0b88c94d-d7b7-4a3f-bd11-5453e5bd94f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mlima_ndiyo-dada-mwalimu-mlima"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mlima"," userResponse":" ndiyo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780120757","data":{"timestamp":" 946780120757"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 0b88c94d-d7b7-4a3f-bd11-5453e5bd94f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mlima_ndiyo-dada-mwalimu-mlima"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mlima"," userResponse":" dada"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780123423","data":{"timestamp":" 946780123423"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 0b88c94d-d7b7-4a3f-bd11-5453e5bd94f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mlima_ndiyo-dada-mwalimu-mlima"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mlima"," userResponse":" mwalimu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780126117","data":{"timestamp":" 946780126117"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 0b88c94d-d7b7-4a3f-bd11-5453e5bd94f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mlima_ndiyo-dada-mwalimu-mlima"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mlima"," userResponse":" mlima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780148710","data":{"timestamp":" 946780148710"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 0b88c94d-d7b7-4a3f-bd11-5453e5bd94f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasi_kimya-tofauti-kasi-pa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kasi"," userResponse":" kimya"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780152607","data":{"timestamp":" 946780152607"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 0b88c94d-d7b7-4a3f-bd11-5453e5bd94f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasi_kimya-tofauti-kasi-pa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kasi"," userResponse":" tofauti"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780155266","data":{"timestamp":" 946780155266"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 0b88c94d-d7b7-4a3f-bd11-5453e5bd94f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasi_kimya-tofauti-kasi-pa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kasi"," userResponse":" kasi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780179947","data":{"timestamp":" 946780179947"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 0b88c94d-d7b7-4a3f-bd11-5453e5bd94f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" barabara_gani-au-kuna-barabara"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" barabara"," userResponse":" gani"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780184057","data":{"timestamp":" 946780184057"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 0b88c94d-d7b7-4a3f-bd11-5453e5bd94f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" barabara_gani-au-kuna-barabara"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" barabara"," userResponse":" au"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780188354","data":{"timestamp":" 946780188354"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 0b88c94d-d7b7-4a3f-bd11-5453e5bd94f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" barabara_gani-au-kuna-barabara"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" barabara"," userResponse":" kuna"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780191749","data":{"timestamp":" 946780191749"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 0b88c94d-d7b7-4a3f-bd11-5453e5bd94f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" barabara_gani-au-kuna-barabara"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" barabara"," userResponse":" barabara"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780210546","data":{"timestamp":" 946780210546"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 0b88c94d-d7b7-4a3f-bd11-5453e5bd94f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gari_mkono-mpira-gari-punde"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" gari"," userResponse":" mkono"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780233215","data":{"timestamp":" 946780233215"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 0b88c94d-d7b7-4a3f-bd11-5453e5bd94f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gari_mkono-mpira-gari-punde"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" gari"," userResponse":" gari"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780269317","data":{"timestamp":" 946780269313"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 0b88c94d-d7b7-4a3f-bd11-5453e5bd94f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" gari_mkono-mpira-gari-punde"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780269453","data":{"timestamp":" 946780269453"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 0b88c94d-d7b7-4a3f-bd11-5453e5bd94f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulitishika ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780282596","data":{"timestamp":" 946780282596"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 4fa47f76-5db3-4d00-9063-370f512cbe2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-J-B"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780286175","data":{"timestamp":" 946780286175"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 4fa47f76-5db3-4d00-9063-370f512cbe2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_Y-U-H"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780290454","data":{"timestamp":" 946780290454"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 4fa47f76-5db3-4d00-9063-370f512cbe2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_U-L-H"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780294511","data":{"timestamp":" 946780294511"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 4fa47f76-5db3-4d00-9063-370f512cbe2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_Y-G-H"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780298563","data":{"timestamp":" 946780298563"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 4fa47f76-5db3-4d00-9063-370f512cbe2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_G-B-H"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780302225","data":{"timestamp":" 946780302225"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 4fa47f76-5db3-4d00-9063-370f512cbe2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-Z-J"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780306283","data":{"timestamp":" 946780306283"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 4fa47f76-5db3-4d00-9063-370f512cbe2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_F-H-D"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780310315","data":{"timestamp":" 946780310315"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 4fa47f76-5db3-4d00-9063-370f512cbe2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_O-H-F"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780314338","data":{"timestamp":" 946780314337"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 4fa47f76-5db3-4d00-9063-370f512cbe2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_O-H-N"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780318250","data":{"timestamp":" 946780318250"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 4fa47f76-5db3-4d00-9063-370f512cbe2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-R-L"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780324037","data":{"timestamp":" 946780324036"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 4fa47f76-5db3-4d00-9063-370f512cbe2f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-R-L"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780336317","data":{"timestamp":" 946780336316"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 91ec6a16-cf98-4f2a-bcfe-b84ff9c5051c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-7-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780342604","data":{"timestamp":" 946780342604"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 91ec6a16-cf98-4f2a-bcfe-b84ff9c5051c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_4-9-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780348420","data":{"timestamp":" 946780348420"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 91ec6a16-cf98-4f2a-bcfe-b84ff9c5051c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_4-9-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780356125","data":{"timestamp":" 946780356125"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 91ec6a16-cf98-4f2a-bcfe-b84ff9c5051c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-5-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780362793","data":{"timestamp":" 946780362793"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 91ec6a16-cf98-4f2a-bcfe-b84ff9c5051c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-2-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780370164","data":{"timestamp":" 946780370164"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 91ec6a16-cf98-4f2a-bcfe-b84ff9c5051c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_8-5-0"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780375489","data":{"timestamp":" 946780375489"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 91ec6a16-cf98-4f2a-bcfe-b84ff9c5051c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-1-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780382579","data":{"timestamp":" 946780382579"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 91ec6a16-cf98-4f2a-bcfe-b84ff9c5051c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_6-1-9"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780390555","data":{"timestamp":" 946780390555"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 91ec6a16-cf98-4f2a-bcfe-b84ff9c5051c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-0-1"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780399461","data":{"timestamp":" 946780399461"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 91ec6a16-cf98-4f2a-bcfe-b84ff9c5051c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_2-4-8"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780406211","data":{"timestamp":" 946780406211"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 91ec6a16-cf98-4f2a-bcfe-b84ff9c5051c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_9-1-0"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780412818","data":{"timestamp":" 946780412817"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 91ec6a16-cf98-4f2a-bcfe-b84ff9c5051c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_1_9-1-0"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780421074","data":{"timestamp":" 946780421073"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 91ec6a16-cf98-4f2a-bcfe-b84ff9c5051c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_1_9-1-0"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780431417","data":{"timestamp":" 946780431416"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780431944","data":{"timestamp":" 946780431944"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780433100","data":{"timestamp":" 946780433099"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780435932","data":{"timestamp":" 946780435931"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780436661","data":{"timestamp":" 946780436661"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780437240","data":{"timestamp":" 946780437240"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780440109","data":{"timestamp":" 946780440108"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780440802","data":{"timestamp":" 946780440801"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780441322","data":{"timestamp":" 946780441321"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780441532","data":{"timestamp":" 946780441531"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780442402","data":{"timestamp":" 946780442402"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" MBAAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780445217","data":{"timestamp":" 946780445216"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780445750","data":{"timestamp":" 946780445750"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780446814","data":{"timestamp":" 946780446813"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780449577","data":{"timestamp":" 946780449575"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780450309","data":{"timestamp":" 946780450309"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780450897","data":{"timestamp":" 946780450896"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780453750","data":{"timestamp":" 946780453750"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780454452","data":{"timestamp":" 946780454452"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780454936","data":{"timestamp":" 946780454936"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780455145","data":{"timestamp":" 946780455143"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780455830","data":{"timestamp":" 946780455830"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780459114","data":{"timestamp":" 946780459114"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780459722","data":{"timestamp":" 946780459722"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780461380","data":{"timestamp":" 946780461379"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPALILIA"," userResponse":" ALIPALILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780462198","data":{"timestamp":" 946780462197"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780462731","data":{"timestamp":" 946780462731"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780463343","data":{"timestamp":" 946780463343"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780466201","data":{"timestamp":" 946780466201"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780466682","data":{"timestamp":" 946780466682"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780468421","data":{"timestamp":" 946780468420"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYUNYIZIA"," userResponse":" ALINYUNYIZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780469203","data":{"timestamp":" 946780469202"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780469746","data":{"timestamp":" 946780469745"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780470324","data":{"timestamp":" 946780470324"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780473317","data":{"timestamp":" 946780473317"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780473591","data":{"timestamp":" 946780473591"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780474307","data":{"timestamp":" 946780474307"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780475134","data":{"timestamp":" 946780475134"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780475837","data":{"timestamp":" 946780475837"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFANYA"," userResponse":" TULIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780476411","data":{"timestamp":" 946780476410"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780477154","data":{"timestamp":" 946780477153"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780477918","data":{"timestamp":" 946780477918"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780478392","data":{"timestamp":" 946780478392"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZO"," userResponse":" HIZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780478933","data":{"timestamp":" 946780478933"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780481315","data":{"timestamp":" 946780481314"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780481616","data":{"timestamp":" 946780481616"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780482167","data":{"timestamp":" 946780482166"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780483119","data":{"timestamp":" 946780483118"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780483716","data":{"timestamp":" 946780483715"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIVUNA"," userResponse":" TULIVUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780484434","data":{"timestamp":" 946780484434"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780484762","data":{"timestamp":" 946780484762"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780485656","data":{"timestamp":" 946780485655"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" MBAAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780488940","data":{"timestamp":" 946780488939"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780489462","data":{"timestamp":" 946780489462"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780489693","data":{"timestamp":" 946780489692"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780490583","data":{"timestamp":" 946780490582"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" MBAAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780491522","data":{"timestamp":" 946780491522"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIZAA"," userResponse":" ILIZAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780492523","data":{"timestamp":" 946780492522"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGUNIA"," userResponse":" MAGUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780492736","data":{"timestamp":" 946780492736"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780493609","data":{"timestamp":" 946780493608"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" MBAAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780496261","data":{"timestamp":" 946780496261"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780496771","data":{"timestamp":" 946780496770"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780496974","data":{"timestamp":" 946780496973"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780497646","data":{"timestamp":" 946780497646"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780498691","data":{"timestamp":" 946780498688"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIZAA"," userResponse":" ILIZAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780499693","data":{"timestamp":" 946780499691"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGUNIA"," userResponse":" MAGUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780499966","data":{"timestamp":" 946780499965"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780500661","data":{"timestamp":" 946780500661"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780503520","data":{"timestamp":" 946780503519"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780504032","data":{"timestamp":" 946780504032"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780505181","data":{"timestamp":" 946780505181"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780508144","data":{"timestamp":" 946780508144"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780508883","data":{"timestamp":" 946780508883"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780509525","data":{"timestamp":" 946780509525"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780512050","data":{"timestamp":" 946780512050"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780512643","data":{"timestamp":" 946780512643"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780513907","data":{"timestamp":" 946780513907"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYOPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIYOPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780514750","data":{"timestamp":" 946780514750"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780514983","data":{"timestamp":" 946780514983"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780515845","data":{"timestamp":" 946780515845"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" MBAAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780518730","data":{"timestamp":" 946780518730"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780519263","data":{"timestamp":" 946780519263"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780520322","data":{"timestamp":" 946780520322"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780523095","data":{"timestamp":" 946780523094"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780523819","data":{"timestamp":" 946780523818"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780524453","data":{"timestamp":" 946780524453"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780526926","data":{"timestamp":" 946780526926"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780527489","data":{"timestamp":" 946780527489"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780528693","data":{"timestamp":" 946780528693"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYOPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIYOPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780529527","data":{"timestamp":" 946780529527"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780529760","data":{"timestamp":" 946780529760"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780530462","data":{"timestamp":" 946780530462"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780533200","data":{"timestamp":" 946780533200"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780533259","data":{"timestamp":" 946780533259"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780540042","data":{"timestamp":" 946780540041"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 65514a4b-e529-4e09-826f-4fa62f2c8aa2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.rise.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780551731","data":{"timestamp":" 946780551731"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 881fe7e1-d39f-4189-a2d0-0cffa8adeb13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.rise.38"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_7-1-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.rise.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780561537","data":{"timestamp":" 946780561537"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 881fe7e1-d39f-4189-a2d0-0cffa8adeb13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.rise.38"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-1-9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.rise.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780571657","data":{"timestamp":" 946780571657"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 881fe7e1-d39f-4189-a2d0-0cffa8adeb13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.rise.38"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-5-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.rise.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780581582","data":{"timestamp":" 946780581582"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 881fe7e1-d39f-4189-a2d0-0cffa8adeb13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.rise.38"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-9-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.rise.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780588717","data":{"timestamp":" 946780588717"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 881fe7e1-d39f-4189-a2d0-0cffa8adeb13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.rise.38"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_9-5-6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.rise.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780595417","data":{"timestamp":" 946780595417"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 881fe7e1-d39f-4189-a2d0-0cffa8adeb13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.rise.38"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_1-0-8"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.rise.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780604147","data":{"timestamp":" 946780604147"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 881fe7e1-d39f-4189-a2d0-0cffa8adeb13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.rise.38"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-2-4"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.rise.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780613272","data":{"timestamp":" 946780613272"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 881fe7e1-d39f-4189-a2d0-0cffa8adeb13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.rise.38"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_7-8-2"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.rise.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780622250","data":{"timestamp":" 946780622250"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 881fe7e1-d39f-4189-a2d0-0cffa8adeb13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.rise.38"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-7-9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.rise.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780631724","data":{"timestamp":" 946780631723"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 881fe7e1-d39f-4189-a2d0-0cffa8adeb13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.rise.38"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6-8"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.rise.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780638309","data":{"timestamp":" 946780638309"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 881fe7e1-d39f-4189-a2d0-0cffa8adeb13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.rise.38"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6-8"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780644803","data":{"timestamp":" 946780644802"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 881fe7e1-d39f-4189-a2d0-0cffa8adeb13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.rise.38"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6-8"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780655858","data":{"timestamp":" 946780655857"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" MIAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780656451","data":{"timestamp":" 946780656450"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINGI"," userResponse":" MINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780657533","data":{"timestamp":" 946780657533"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOPITA"," userResponse":" ILIYOPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780658524","data":{"timestamp":" 946780658524"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUSI"," userResponse":" MJUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780658720","data":{"timestamp":" 946780658720"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780659170","data":{"timestamp":" 946780659170"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780659919","data":{"timestamp":" 946780659918"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780660872","data":{"timestamp":" 946780660872"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miaka mingi iliyopita Mjusi na Chura walikuwa marafiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780663284","data":{"timestamp":" 946780663283"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780663927","data":{"timestamp":" 946780663927"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780665115","data":{"timestamp":" 946780665114"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMUA"," userResponse":" WALIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780666056","data":{"timestamp":" 946780666056"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUTAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780666819","data":{"timestamp":" 946780666819"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" WASICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780667613","data":{"timestamp":" 946780667613"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPENZI"," userResponse":" WAPENZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780668416","data":{"timestamp":" 946780668415"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja waliamua kutafuta wasichana wapenzi jijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJINI"," userResponse":" JIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780671151","data":{"timestamp":" 946780671151"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780672224","data":{"timestamp":" 946780672224"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWONEA"," userResponse":" ALIMWONEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780672848","data":{"timestamp":" 946780672847"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUSI"," userResponse":" MJUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780673632","data":{"timestamp":" 946780673632"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIVU"," userResponse":" WIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780674161","data":{"timestamp":" 946780674160"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780674541","data":{"timestamp":" 946780674541"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780675072","data":{"timestamp":" 946780675071"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" NGOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780675454","data":{"timestamp":" 946780675453"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780676957","data":{"timestamp":" 946780676957"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIMETAMETA"," userResponse":" ILIMETAMETA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780677481","data":{"timestamp":" 946780677481"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780678373","data":{"timestamp":" 946780678373"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chura alimwonea Mjusi wivu kwa vile ngozi yake ilimetameta na kuvutia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUTIA"," userResponse":" KUVUTIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780681621","data":{"timestamp":" 946780681621"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780682818","data":{"timestamp":" 946780682817"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPI"," userResponse":" KIPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780683515","data":{"timestamp":" 946780683515"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIFANYA"," userResponse":" ULIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780683992","data":{"timestamp":" 946780683992"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780684866","data":{"timestamp":" 946780684865"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAONEKANA"," userResponse":" UKAONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780685379","data":{"timestamp":" 946780685378"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780686267","data":{"timestamp":" 946780686267"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780688612","data":{"timestamp":" 946780688612"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780689908","data":{"timestamp":" 946780689907"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIANGALIE"," userResponse":" NIANGALIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780690811","data":{"timestamp":" 946780690811"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780691299","data":{"timestamp":" 946780691299"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SURA"," userResponse":" SURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780692009","data":{"timestamp":" 946780692008"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" MBAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780692423","data":{"timestamp":" 946780692422"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu niangalie nina sura mbaya mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780695395","data":{"timestamp":" 946780695395"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAWEZA"," userResponse":" NINAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780695888","data":{"timestamp":" 946780695888"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780696633","data":{"timestamp":" 946780696632"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780697415","data":{"timestamp":" 946780697415"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUSU"," userResponse":" KUHUSU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780697978","data":{"timestamp":" 946780697978"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" NGOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780698772","data":{"timestamp":" 946780698772"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninaweza kufanya nini kuhusu ngozi yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780701799","data":{"timestamp":" 946780701799"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUSI"," userResponse":" MJUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780702697","data":{"timestamp":" 946780702695"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780704200","data":{"timestamp":" 946780704199"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKILIZA"," userResponse":" SIKILIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780706507","data":{"timestamp":" 946780706506"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIA"," userResponse":" TIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780707154","data":{"timestamp":" 946780707153"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780708214","data":{"timestamp":" 946780708213"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGUNI"," userResponse":" CHUNGUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780709024","data":{"timestamp":" 946780709023"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780709915","data":{"timestamp":" 946780709915"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKIWEKE"," userResponse":" UKIWEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780710646","data":{"timestamp":" 946780710646"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tia maji chunguni kisha ukiweke mekoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEKONI"," userResponse":" MEKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780713523","data":{"timestamp":" 946780713523"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu u..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780713579","data":{"timestamp":" 946780713579"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu u..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780717274","data":{"timestamp":" 946780717273"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780717690","data":{"timestamp":" 946780717690"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780718331","data":{"timestamp":" 946780718331"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780719146","data":{"timestamp":" 946780719145"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" NAJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780719859","data":{"timestamp":" 946780719859"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780720708","data":{"timestamp":" 946780720707"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Chura akasema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" NAJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780723103","data":{"timestamp":" 946780723102"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fyata ulimi rafiki yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FYATA"," userResponse":" FYATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780723929","data":{"timestamp":" 946780723929"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fyata ulimi rafiki yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMI"," userResponse":" ULIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780724441","data":{"timestamp":" 946780724441"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fyata ulimi rafiki yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780724798","data":{"timestamp":" 946780724798"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fyata ulimi rafiki yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780727314","data":{"timestamp":" 946780727313"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akaondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780728837","data":{"timestamp":" 946780728837"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mara akaondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAONDOKA"," userResponse":" AKAONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780731945","data":{"timestamp":" 946780731944"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780732553","data":{"timestamp":" 946780732553"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780733331","data":{"timestamp":" 946780733331"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKA"," userResponse":" ALIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780734176","data":{"timestamp":" 946780734175"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780734536","data":{"timestamp":" 946780734536"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780735171","data":{"timestamp":" 946780735171"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTIA"," userResponse":" KUTIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780735643","data":{"timestamp":" 946780735643"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780736457","data":{"timestamp":" 946780736457"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alifika nyumbani na kutia maji chunguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGUNI"," userResponse":" CHUNGUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780739647","data":{"timestamp":" 946780739646"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780740523","data":{"timestamp":" 946780740522"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIPOANZA"," userResponse":" YALIPOANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780741429","data":{"timestamp":" 946780741428"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEMKA"," userResponse":" KUCHEMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780743424","data":{"timestamp":" 946780743423"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJITUMBUKIZA"," userResponse":" ALIJITUMBUKIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780743925","data":{"timestamp":" 946780743924"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yalipoanza kuchemka alijitumbukiza ndani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780746576","data":{"timestamp":" 946780746576"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780747169","data":{"timestamp":" 946780747168"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOZI"," userResponse":" NGOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780747540","data":{"timestamp":" 946780747540"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780748723","data":{"timestamp":" 946780748722"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKACHOMEKA"," userResponse":" IKACHOMEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780749184","data":{"timestamp":" 946780749184"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780749713","data":{"timestamp":" 946780749711"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780750140","data":{"timestamp":" 946780750140"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780751171","data":{"timestamp":" 946780751170"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" na ngozi yake ikachomeka na mkia wake ukakatika!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAKATIKA"," userResponse":" UKAKATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780753865","data":{"timestamp":" 946780753865"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780754478","data":{"timestamp":" 946780754476"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADALA"," userResponse":" BADALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780754681","data":{"timestamp":" 946780754681"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780755720","data":{"timestamp":" 946780755720"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMETAMETA"," userResponse":" KUMETAMETA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780755926","data":{"timestamp":" 946780755925"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780756321","data":{"timestamp":" 946780756320"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780756966","data":{"timestamp":" 946780756965"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780757383","data":{"timestamp":" 946780757382"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780758055","data":{"timestamp":" 946780758055"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJUSI"," userResponse":" MJUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780759317","data":{"timestamp":" 946780759316"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780759581","data":{"timestamp":" 946780759580"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780760194","data":{"timestamp":" 946780760194"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SURA"," userResponse":" SURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780761033","data":{"timestamp":" 946780761033"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" MBAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780761693","data":{"timestamp":" 946780761693"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780764207","data":{"timestamp":" 946780764203"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780764281","data":{"timestamp":" 946780764281"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" f9dc6f3a-cba0-4edb-946f-a84c275e91e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780776345","data":{"timestamp":" 946780776345"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 64f430e5-ccbc-402b-8d3e-d65983f334fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" IMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780779865","data":{"timestamp":" 946780779865"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 64f430e5-ccbc-402b-8d3e-d65983f334fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780781435","data":{"timestamp":" 946780781435"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 64f430e5-ccbc-402b-8d3e-d65983f334fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ILIKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" ILIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780785186","data":{"timestamp":" 946780785185"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 64f430e5-ccbc-402b-8d3e-d65983f334fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ILIKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780786745","data":{"timestamp":" 946780786745"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 64f430e5-ccbc-402b-8d3e-d65983f334fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" INGIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGIA"," userResponse":" INGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780790793","data":{"timestamp":" 946780790792"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 64f430e5-ccbc-402b-8d3e-d65983f334fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" INGIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780792346","data":{"timestamp":" 946780792346"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 64f430e5-ccbc-402b-8d3e-d65983f334fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" IMEJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780796244","data":{"timestamp":" 946780796244"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 64f430e5-ccbc-402b-8d3e-d65983f334fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780798259","data":{"timestamp":" 946780798259"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 64f430e5-ccbc-402b-8d3e-d65983f334fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780798420","data":{"timestamp":" 946780798420"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 64f430e5-ccbc-402b-8d3e-d65983f334fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780811841","data":{"timestamp":" 946780811841"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 4ef5d8a3-16c9-40fc-be23-797502e06ecc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_3-4-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780818125","data":{"timestamp":" 946780818124"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 4ef5d8a3-16c9-40fc-be23-797502e06ecc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-7-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780824485","data":{"timestamp":" 946780824485"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 4ef5d8a3-16c9-40fc-be23-797502e06ecc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-7-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780829116","data":{"timestamp":" 946780829115"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 4ef5d8a3-16c9-40fc-be23-797502e06ecc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-7-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780852873","data":{"timestamp":" 946780852873"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 4ef5d8a3-16c9-40fc-be23-797502e06ecc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_4-5-9"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780857383","data":{"timestamp":" 946780857383"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 4ef5d8a3-16c9-40fc-be23-797502e06ecc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_4-5-9"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946780863701","data":{"timestamp":" 946780863701"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_050835"," gameId":" 4ef5d8a3-16c9-40fc-be23-797502e06ecc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_5_4-5-9"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}